The Queen's name is...
Maria Kisaragi.
Is that right?
I-I don't know...
The only name Lady Kisaragi
goes by is Lady Kisaragi.
Our headquarters is in Kawaguchi, Saitama.
Thank God I know so little...
She'll be safe!
I see. Then can you tell me about
the structure of your group?
Does this guy...
...know who the Queen is?
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Let's get started.
Gobo-kun, I hate to trouble you,
but can you give me a hand?
Sure thing, for real!
The enemy is located near Kawaguchi
Station in Kawaguchi, Saitama.
The group's leader is the Queen,
a woman named Kisaragi.
Queen
Maria Kisaragi
She has a personal entourage
called the "Three Powers".
The striker is Ikusa Garai.
Three Powers
Ikusa Garai
Supported by Meguru Tsukioka.
Meguru Tsukioka
And Kou Kirishima is the brains.
Kou Kirishima
Under that are lower officers
who work the front line,
Front line
which includes Touya Mutsuki and
another striker named Knight Kato.
And an additional support member, Lili Kato.
These seven are the enemy structure
we've gathered from him.
Touya Mutsuki and the other front line members
were recently promoted to replace
Hikari Ebina and Hirayama.
So he knows barely
any internal information
and practically nothing of the
other members' Rights and abilities.
If we piece together all of our information,
we can determine Ikusa, Meguru,
Touya, and Knight's Prime Rights.
Gobo, can you display
each of their Prime Rights?
You got it!
So we're missing information on...
Kisaragi the Queen, Kou of the Three Powers,
and the front line member Lili.
We've yet to identify
the Rights of these three.
So what next?
We've figured out their location,
so do we plan an attack?
No. With Touya's disappearance, the Queen
likely assumed they've been compromised
and has already either fled or set a trap.
And besides, we let those
other members go, remember?
If my theory is correct, that
should make her quite uneasy.
What do you mean?
By the way, there's no such thing
as Stage Three, is there?
Do you guys have a back-up plan?
That's no problem!
The start time was announced
as 10:00 PM, but we've already
scheduled a text message to go out
at 9:50 PM to delay it! For real!
I figured that's why
you announced a start time.
You mean he had my
entire plan figured out?
So, wait... Will the Queen be pissed,
now that she's been tricked?
Oh man...
We'll split up in groups after this.
Let's see...
Ichinose-kun, Jin-kun, Kunashiri-kun,
could the three of you come with me?
The rest of you will wait
in the lobby with me.
Okay!
Hey, Yagihashi...
Hm?
Do you know the Queen personally?
I don't know exactly who the Queen is.
That's all I can say for now...
Can we really trust this guy?
There's no such thing
as the Control Right?!
That was their plan...
We're relocating.
Get everything prepared.
They likely used the Suspension Right
to freeze Knight's attack.
Which means...
It must be Tojuro Yagihashi!
You two must have had quite the reunion.
Y-Yeah...
He only got what he deserved!
You dummy, Kazuhiko!
Now...
Are we all set with the audio and video?
We're good!
I'm about to tell you
something very important.
This guy is...
Saneatsu Narita?
Saaya! Saaya!
Don't touch them!
During the ambush operation,
we were under the impression that
the Emperor would be defeated
using Narita-kun's Parental Authority...
But that wasn't the case, was it?
What?
They didn't use Parental Authority?
You see—
I'll tell them.
Sane sacrificed himself to carry out a
strategy with the best chance of success.
We baited the Emperor into
taking a tally that would kill all of us.
A question for those within the 210th floor of the Emperor's tower.
Are you part of Team Saneatsu?
He thought he won, which created an opening
to beat him with a remote attack.
Die
To avoid being subject to the tally,
I fused with the cells of his puppets,
and Omi used his Rejection Right,
leaving the two of us to survive.
But Sane and Saaya didn't...
That idiot...
You mean they're both dead?
They're never going to wake up?
Well, that depends.
For example,
what if I set my Suspension Right to halt time
when the two of them were
faced with imminent death?
Don't tell me that...
You mean...
I told you, I wanted to
focus on supporting everyone.
So the two of them are alive?
Yagi-chan, great job!
Get off of me!
Holy crap, for real.
Yeah.
But whether or not
they'll survive is still 50/50.
Why is that?
This is a different scenario from Sato-kun's.
In this case, the conditions
of Tasuketsu become an issue.
In other words, when exactly
was death established?
Man or Woman
The Suspension Right was set
to activate prior to death,
so right before midnight.
If death was established exactly at midnight,
I'd have stopped time beforehand,
Announcement
Suspension
Establishment
Execution
so they'd live even after
I deactivate the Suspension Right.
However, if death was established the moment
the question was displayed at 23:58 PM,
their predetermined death
would be waiting for them
after I deactivate my Suspension Right.
Since we don't know which is true,
deactivating my Suspension Right
could result in their deaths.
No way...
Let's do it!
It means there's still hope.
Thanks, Yagi-chan.
Then let's go home... together.
Whoa... The Induction Right is so cool...
He's the true brains...
By the way, what are you gonna do
about that Mutsuki dude?
He'll be leaving us soon with the
Explosion Right I set a little bit ago.
Good bye, Touya Mutsuki.
Sweet dreams...
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Damn it!
We're relocating?
You seem dissatisfied, Ikusa Garai.
Kou...
Lady Kisaragi's orders are final.
If you can't obey her wishes, then—
I know, shut up!
I'm just not happy about it, that's all.
Same goes for you, Kou.
As the Three Powers, we're equal, right?
Then why are you her closest aide?
Stop acting so special!
I'm...
I'm nothing but a useful servant.
There's nothing special about me.
You're simply misunderstanding
my circumstance...
He's so full of it.
I will take your place one day!
Watch out, coming through!
S-So what's up calling me
over all the sudden, hag?
It's about your loss in this battle.
Perhaps it couldn't be helped considering
your opponent was Tojuro Yagihashi,
but you may have had a chance
to win had you put in more work.
W-Wait a second!
Come on, I tried!
I tried real hard! Please!
The results speak for themselves...
As the first person on the front line, I trust
this loss will give you better awareness.
Th-Then what about Mom?
As for her, I'll let it slide just this time.
But I've taken your
little sister Lili in return.
Wha—Why Lili?!
Hush.
If you want me to free her, work harder.
You stupid hag!
How's Lili?
She's fine. We're still
keeping her under narcosis.
But are you sure about this?
It can't be helped.
For some reason, I can't undo
the Rights of Knight and Lili.
Knight's Destruction Right is one of the
strongest under the Transmutation Attribute,
right behind the Division Right
and Induction Right.
There's nothing I won't do
to keep it within our grasp.
Family-loving kids like him are best used
when threatened with hostages.
I see. That's very convincing, indeed.
Kou. You do understand, don't you?
You need not worry, milady.
We'll be the ones left standing...
We've got all the help we need,
as long as we have Yagi-chan and Sudocchi.
Don't forget me! I can blow stuff up!
Shut up, antenna head.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Yagihashi...
That guy's....
What's wrong?
You seem lost in thought.
I know what you're thinking.
You can trust me. We're on the same team.
He's way ahead of me...
There's no way I can outsmart him.
What am I doing here?
Am I... useless?
What's wrong?
You not feeling well?
Nah, it's nothing...
Hey, what are you—
Don't keep it bottled up. Speak up.
We're your elders, you know.
Elders...
I wonder what Kazuki would say?
I'm just feeling sad and a bit down.
You used your—
Maybe you should have kept your guard up!
You didn't resist, which means
I'm using my Obedience Right!
Go ahead and let it all out.
It's not like I can fight,
and you've got better
strategists than me now...
Am I even needed here?
At this point, what am I to you guys?
You're one of us, duh.
Raion, that's what you were so worried about?
But I can't do anything remotely special...
You know Saaya?
Huh?
Oh yeah, her...
She was the same as you.
She didn't possess any Rights, but
she was always ready to risk it all.
Yet she was an important member
of our group until the end.
There's no rhyme or reason
to being a true friend.
I can't explain it, but you just care about
each other and want to be together.
You're great just as you are, Raion.
No rhyme or reason...
Is it really that simple?
Don't ever change yourself.
You really were right...
Before, I wanted to save the world because
it was the only place I shared with Kazuki...
But now...
I want to defeat the Queen,
and protect you guys!
We know how you feel.
Yeah.
I may be a bit timid, but—
We're all the same.
Yup.
Mm-yup!
Where did you all come from?!
My dear people, I understand!
Your Emperor Rahatzelt shares your conviction!
I am moved by the masses!
You're still doing that shtick?
Super lame.
So mean... for real!
Hey guys!
Rika!
They seem to be having fun...
I thought I wanted to be alone,
so why am I tagging along with you guys?
We all just gathered where we felt like it.
You're right...
Now...
let's begin our strategy meeting
to take down the Queen.
Everything we already know, they've
likely made plans to counter.
Yeah, that's true.
Our findings are useless
if they've overhauled their location
and team structure...
But that's only true for the future.
They can't change the past.
The key to our recent findings
lies in their past.
The past? What do you mean?
One notable factor is the member Knight Kato.
There was a moment when he used his
Destruction Right without declaring its name.
So the Destruction Right doesn't
belong to the Production Attribute.
I'm certain it's under
the Transmutation Attribute.
So he can use his Prime Right as much as
he wants without draining his stamina?
Exactly.
The Queen's actions so far show that she
assumes the current Emperor resides in Tokyo.
Then why not simply annihilate Tokyo
itself with the Destruction Right?
Annihilate?!
Yes.
In combination with Mutsuki's Gravity Right,
it would have been an easy plan to execute.
So why didn't she do that?
Even if we noticed and attempted to run,
she could have easily stopped us.
How?
For example...
Use the Destruction Right to create rubble,
the Exchange Right to send
it to prefecture borders,
and finally the Duplication Right
to physically block us from leaving Tokyo.
True. It's not flashy, but it's certainly
an effective countermeasure.
It could have been one of her options.
Good point...
I guess it's plausible that she'd
use forcible measures like that...
She did say that she'd use whatever
means were necessary to kill us.
I could see her going to those lengths.
So what if we reverse that logic?
On the one hand, she could have annihilated Tokyo
while not knowing the Emperor's whereabouts.
So why would she avoid annihilating
Tokyo in the same circumstance?
There's someone or something
she doesn't want destroyed,
and she can't annihilate Tokyo
without putting it in danger?
It's merely a hypothesis, but yes.
But how would that hypothesis
affect our plan at all?
We'll shut down Tokyo.
What?
Shut down Tokyo?
I'm completely lost right now.
Hear us out.
Let's call this something or someone "X".
Say "X" truly does exist somewhere in Tokyo.
If Tokyo falls under the control
of the current Emperor,
that could mean handing
over "X" to the Emperor.
And the Queen would be forced to act...
Precisely.
This way, we can determine
the probability of "X"'s existence
based on the Queen's actions.
If "X" does exist, we keep it
alive, no question.
I'm personally curious as to what it is.
The Queen may act regardless of if "X" exists,
but if she doesn't act at all,
we can conclude "X" doesn't exist.
But how will we even shut down Tokyo anyway?
There's no way to know the enemy's actions.
We only need to pretend to shut it down.
Our true purpose is to find out
where their headquarters is.
Shinozaki.
Souma.
We'll use your Prime Rights to monitor people
moving in and out of Tokyo from the skies.
Let's materialize clouds just in case,
and make sure the moonlight
doesn't cast your shadows.
We'll limit our search to those
with descriptions that match our targets.
Share the location and appearance
of those you check...
Itabashi Station. Male with mohawk.
...and we'll display them with the
Presentation Right for further monitoring.
Display Itabashi Station's mohawk dude!
I see. It's possible.
Then we can let them roam free
back to headquarters,
and we may not just find their
location, but the Queen herself!
Hang on. Do you think they'll even
believe that we shut down Tokyo?
Probably.
You've shown your Materialization Right
to the Three Powers, right?
Yeah.
Mutsuki mentioned that the Queen
informed him of the Response Right.
If the Queen is knowledgeable
about the Rights, she must realize
that we can do practically anything
with the Materialization Right.
Still, I can only materialize
three times a day max.
I doubt they'd believe
we can shut down Tokyo—
Actually, I don't think they know that part.
That Meguru chick knew
about the Rejection Right,
but didn't know its effects last 72 hours.
That's how she fell for my trap.
Good point.
The Queen's knowledge is still limited.
She likely knows about different
Rights and their basic abilities,
but not in too much in detail.
I'm starting to get confused!
We just need to convince them
we can, that's all.
Just like we don't know
their plans and intentions,
they're in the dark about us, too.
Let's leverage that.
In order to maintain the upper hand,
we'll have to bluff a little.
We'll call it the Tokyo Blockade Operation.
The plan will commence tomorrow.
We'll announce our blockade,
and Souma and Shinozaki will
monitor the ground from the skies.
Subjects will be monitored until
we identify the enemy's headquarters.
Then we'll ambush them, and...
Team
...take them down!